Find the wonder, find the joy, find the magic
Us Again is a animation, drama, family film directed by Zach Parrish.
In a vibrant city pulsating with rhythm and movement, an elderly man and his young-at-heart wife
rekindle their youthful passion for life and each other on one magical night.
Us Again is a 2021 American animated short film directed and written by Zach
Parrish and distributed by Walt Disney Studios Motion Pictures.
It follows Art, a grumpy old man, and Dot, his
energetic wife, in a vibrant city of dance.
The two enjoy themselves in a rainstorm that makes them young
until it disappears and reverts them back to old age.
Parrish conceived Us Again after noticing that he was growing
older and took inspiration from his grandparents.
Its score, composed by Pinar Toprak, was written before storyboarding
and animation, unlike the typical filmmaking process.
For dance reference, Disney hired choreographers Keone and Mari Madrid.
Us Again was released on March 5, 2021, preceding
theatrical showings of Raya and the Last Dragon.
The short has received positive reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of new york city, dancing, rain, musical, lovers.
The tone is emotional.